Guide to the New American Library Archive 1943-1962 MSS.070
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: New American Library, Editorial/Author Files
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "The Courting of Susie Brown," 1949-53, 1958-60, 1949-1960 (Box 17, Folder 284)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Episode in Palmetto,", 1950-1958 (Box 17, Folder 285)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Georgia Boy,", 1949-1961 (Box 18, Folder 286)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "God's Little Acre," 1946, 1948-1957, 1946-1957 (Box 18, Folder 287)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "God's Little Acre,", 1957-1961 (Box 18, Folder 288)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Gretta," "Gulf Coast Stories,", 1955-1959 (Box 18, Folder 289)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "A House in the Uplands," "The Humorous Side," 1948-53, 1955, 1957-60, 1948-1960 (Box 18, Folder 290)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Jenny by Nature," "Journeyman," 1947-53, 1956-62, 1947-1962 (Box 18, Folder 291)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Kneel to the Rising Sun," "A Lamp for Nightfall," 1950-54, 1957-61, 1950-1961 (Box 18, Folder 292)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Love and Money," "Men and Women,", 1954-1961 (Box 19, Folder 293)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Place Called Estherville," "Southways,", 1950-1960 (Box 19, Folder 294)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "The Sure Hand of God," "A Swell-Looking Girl" ("American Earth"), 1947-1961 (Box 19, Folder 295)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "This Very Earth," "Tobacco Road,", 1946-1961 (Box 19, Folder 296)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Tobacco Road" (play by Jack Kirkland), 1951-1958 (Box 19, Folder 297)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "Tragic Ground," "Trouble in July,", 1946-1959 (Box 19, Folder 298)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "We Are the Living,", 1950-1960 (Box 19, Folder 299)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, "When You Think of Me," "Where the Girls Are Different," "A Woman in the House", 1948-51, 1958-60, 1948-1960 (Box 20, Folder 300)
  - Caldwell, Erskine, Caldwell magazine project (Almat Publishing), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 301)
  - Calitri, Charles, "Strike Heaven on the Face,", 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 302)
  - Callaghan, Morley, "The Loved and the Lost," 1950-53, 1955, 1958-60, 1950-1960 (Box 20, Folder 303)
  - Calmer, Ned, "The Strange Land,", 1950-1960 (Box 20, Folder 304)
  - Cantwell, Robert, general correspondence, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 305)
  - Capote, Truman, general correspondence, "Breakfast at Tiffany's," "The Grass Harp," 1951-54, 1956-61, 1951-1961 (Box 20, Folder 306)
  - Capote, Truman, "A Tree of Night," "A Tree of Night and The Grass Harp," "Other Voices, Other Rooms," 1948-54, 1956-57, 1960-61, 1948-1961 (Box 20, Folder 307)
  - Carreno, Jose-Suarez, "The Final Hours,", 1952-1954 (Box 20, Folder 308)
  - Carrington, Richard, "A Biography of the Sea,", 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 309)
  - Carroll, Lewis, "Alice in Wonderland,", 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 310)
  - Carson, Rachel, "The Edge of the Sea,", 1956-1959 (Box 21, Folder 311)
  - Carson, Rachel, "The Sea Around Us,", 1951-1960 (Box 21, Folder 312)
  - Carson, Rachel, "Under the Sea Wind,", 1953-1960 (Box 21, Folder 313)
  - Carter, Ross S., "Those Devils in Baggy Pants,", 1951-1959 (Box 21, Folder 314)
  - Cassill, R.V., "Dormitory Women,", 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 315)
  - Cather, Willa, "The Troll Garden,", 1961 (Box 21, Folder 316)
  - Caulfield, M.F., "The Black City,", 1952, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 317)
  - Cela, Camilo Jose, "The Hive,", 1953-1958 (Box 21, Folder 318)
  - Chai, Chu, "The Changing Society in China,", 1961 (Box 21, Folder 319)
  - Chamales, Tom, general correspondence, "Go Naked in the World," Never So Few,", 1959-1961 (Box 21, Folder 320)
  - Chambliss, William, "The Silent Service,", 1957 (Box 21, Folder 321)
  - Chambliss, William, "The Silent Service,", 1958 (Box 21, Folder 322)
  - Chandler, David, "The Man in the Middle,", 1960 (Box 21, Folder 323)
  - Chang, Diana, "The Havana Story," 1952; Chanslor, Ray, "The Ballad of Cat Ballou," 1961, 1952, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 324)
  - Chase, Borden, "Ataturk,", 1960 (Box 21, Folder 325)
  - Chase, James Hadley, general correspondence, "The Case of the Strangled Starlet," "Not Safe to be Free,", 1952-1959 (Box 22, Folder 326)
  - Chase, James Hadley, "The Double Shuffle," "I'll Bury My Dead," "The Guilty are Afraid," "Shock Treatment,", 1952-1959 (Box 22, Folder 327)
  - Chase, Richard, general correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 22, Folder 328)
  - Chase, Richard, general correspondence, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 329)
  - Chase, Richard, general correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 22, Folder 330)
  - Chase, Richard, musical scores (no date), undated (Box 22, Folder 331)
  - Chase, Richard, general correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 22, Folder 332)
  - Chase, Richard, general correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 333)
  - Chase, Richard, memoranda, 1949-1957 (Box 23, Folder 334)
  - Chase, Richard, memoranda, 1954-1956 (Box 23, Folder 335)
  - Chase, Richard, memoranda (no date), undated (Box 23, Folder 336)
  - Chayefsky, Paddy, "The Bachelor Party,", 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 337)
  - Cheney, L.J., "A Brief History of Western Civilization,", 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 338)
  - Chesser, Eustace, "How to Make a Success of Your Marriage,", 1953-1957 (Box 23, Folder 339)
  - Chesser, Eustace, "Love Without Fear,", 1949-1961 (Box 23, Folder 340)
  - Childe, V. Gordon, "Man Makes Himself,", 1950-1961 (Box 23, Folder 341)
  - Childe, V. Gordon, "What Happened in History,", 1945-1958 (Box 23, Folder 342)
  - Childs, Marquis, "Ethics in a Business Society,", 1951-1960 (Box 23, Folder 343)
  - Childs, Marquis, "Ethics in a Business Society,", 1952-1960 (Box 24, Folder 344)
  - Childs, Marquis, "Sweden,", 1946-1961 (Box 24, Folder 345)
  - Christensen, Erwin, "The Growth of Western Art,", 1957-1961 (Box 24, Folder 346)
  - Christensen, Erwin, "The Growth of Western Art,", 1958 (Box 24, Folder 347)
  - Christensen, Erwin, "The Growth of Western Art,", 1959-1960 (Box 24, Folder 348)
  - Christensen, Erwin, "The Growth of Western Art," no date, undated (Box 24, Folder 349)
  - Christian Herald, The, "Courage and Confidence,", 1950-1954 (Box 24, Folder 350)
  - Christian Herald, The, "Courage and Confidence" (manuscript), 1950 (Box 25, Folder 351)
  - Christman, Henry L., general correspondence, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 352)
  - Chute, Marchette, "Stories from Shakespeare,", 1956-1961 (Box 25, Folder 353)
  - Ciardi, John, "Purgatorio,", 1953-1962 (Box 25, Folder 354)
  - Ciardi, John, "Purgatorio,", 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 355)
  - Ciardi, John, "Purgatorio,", 1961 (Box 25, Folder 356)
  - Ciardi, John, "Inferno,", 1952-1953 (Box 25, Folder 357)
  - Ciardi, John, "Inferno,", 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 358)
  - Ciardi, John, "Inferno,", 1954 (Box 26, Folder 359)
  - Ciardi, John, "Inferno,", 1955-1961 (Box 26, Folder 360)
  - Claggett, John, "The Slot,", 1958-1960 (Box 26, Folder 361)
  - Clark, Christopher, "Good is for Angels,", 1950-1960 (Box 26, Folder 362)
  - Clark, Manning, "A History of Australia,", 1960 (Box 26, Folder 363)
  - Clark, Walter Van Tilberg, "Ox-Bow Incident," "Track of the Cat,", 1943-1961 (Box 26, Folder 364)
  - Clark, Walter Van Tilberg, "Track of the Cat," "Watchful Gods,", 1950-1961 (Box 26, Folder 365)
  - Clarke, Arthur, "The City and the Stars," "The Deep Range," "Islands in the Sky," "The Other Side of the Sky,", 1955-1960 (Box 26, Folder 366)
  - Clippinger, Frances, "Elinda" ("The Satellite"), 1950-1952 (Box 26, Folder 367)
  - Cloete, Stuart, "The Curve and the Tusk,", 1952-1961 (Box 26, Folder 368)
  - Cobb, Walter J., "Atala," "Rene," "Princess of Cleves,", 1956 (Box 26, Folder 369)
  - Coe, Charles Francis, "Ashes," "Pressure,", 1951, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 370)
  - Coen, Franklin, general correspondence; Cohen, Louis H., "Murder, Madness, and the Law," 1952-60, 1952-1960 (Box 27, Folder 371)
  - Coleman, James A.., "Origin and Structure of the Universe,", 1958-1960 (Box 27, Folder 372)
  - Coleman, James A., "Relativity for the Layman,", 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 373)
  - Colette, general correspondence, "Cheri," "Last of Cheri," "Game of Love," "Ripening Seed," 1948, 1950-61, 1948-1961 (Box 27, Folder 374)
  - Colette, "Gigi," "Julie de Carneilhan," "The Tender Shoot," 1947, 1950-54, 1957-61, 1947-1961 (Box 27, Folder 375)
  - Collier, John, general correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 27, Folder 376)
  - Collier, John, general correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 27, Folder 377)
  - Collier, John, "Indians of the Americas,", 1949-1956 (Box 27, Folder 378)
  - Collier, John, "Indians of the Americas,", 1957-1961 (Box 28, Folder 379)
  - Collier, John, "Indians of the Americas" (Fred Marsh, ed), 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 380)
  - Collier, John, "Indians of the Americas" (Arabel J. Porter, ed), 1947-49, 1955-56, 1958-59, 1947-1959 (Box 28, Folder 381)
  - Collier, John [British novelist], "Defy the Foul Fiend,", 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 382)
  - Collins, Carvel, "On Faulkner," 1946-57, 1959; Colt, Clem, "Quick Trigger Country", 1946-1959 (Box 28, Folder 383)
  - Commager, Henry Steele, "America in Perspective," 1945-55, 1957-60, 1945-1960 (Box 28, Folder 384)
  - Conant, James B., "On Understanding Science,", 1950-1960 (Box 28, Folder 385)
  - Condon, Richard, "The Manchurian Candidate,", 1959-1961 (Box 28, Folder 386)
  - Connell, Vivian, "The Golden Sleep," "Hounds of Cloneen", undated (Box 28, Folder 387)
  - Conrad, Joseph, general correspondence, undated (Box 28, Folder 388)
  - Conrad, Joseph, "Almayer's Folly," "Heart of Darkness," "The Secret Sharer," 1948-53, 1955-59, 1948-1959 (Box 29, Folder 389)
  - Conrad, Joseph, "Heart of Darkness," "Lord Jim," "Nostromo,", 1959-1961 (Box 29, Folder 390)
  - Constant, Benjamin, "Adolphe," "The Red Notebook,", 1958-1960 (Box 29, Folder 391)
  - Conton, William, "The African,"1958-59, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 392)
  - Conton, William, "The African,", 1959 (Box 29, Folder 393)
  - Conton, William, "The African,", 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 394)
  - Cooley, Donald G., general correspondence, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 395)
  - Coon, Horace, general correspondence, 1953-1961 (Box 30, Folder 396)
  - Coon, Horace, "43,000 Years Later,", 1955-1957 (Box 30, Folder 397)
  - Coon, Horace, "43,000 Years Later,", 1957-1959 (Box 30, Folder 398)
  - Coon, Horace, "Hobbies for Fun and Profit,", 1953-1955 (Box 30, Folder 399)
  - Coon, Horace, "How to Be a Member,", 1952-1955 (Box 30, Folder 400)
  - Coon, Horace, "How to Be a Member,", 1956 (Box 30, Folder 401)
  - Coon, Horace, "Speak Better, Write Better English," 1953-60, 1962, 1953-1962 (Box 30, Folder 402)
  - Coon, Horace, "Better Words for Better Living,", 1957-1959 (Box 30, Folder 403)
  - Cooper, James Fenimore, "The Pathfinder,", 1960-1961 (Box 31, Folder 404)
  - Cooper, Mae, "Lily Henry,", 1949-1951 (Box 31, Folder 405)
  - Copland, Aaron, "What to Listen for in Music," 1952-60, "Music & Imagination," 1958-59, 1952-1960 (Box 31, Folder 406)
  - Cordall, Alexander, "The Rape of the Fair Country,", 1959 (Box 31, Folder 407)
  - Cornwall, I.W., "Natural Environments & Archaelogy,", 1960 (Box 31, Folder 408)
  - Costentino, Ruth, "How to Know French Antiques,", 1959-1961 (Box 31, Folder 409)
  - Cotlow, Lewis, "Amazon Headhunters,", 1953-1959 (Box 31, Folder 410)
  - Cottrell, Leonard, general correspondence, 1948-1959 (Box 31, Folder 411)
  - Cottrell, Leonard, "The Anvil of Civilization,", 1954-1960 (Box 31, Folder 412)
  - Cottrell, Leonard, "The Anvil of Civilization," (no date), undated (Box 31, Folder 413)
  - Court, Nathan A., "Mathematics in Fun & Earnest,", 1958-1961 (Box 31, Folder 414)
  - Cox, William R., "Comanche Moon, " "Duke's Honor, " "Hell to Pay,", 1958-1961 (Box 31, Folder 415)
  - Cox, William R., "Hell to Pay, ", 1958-1961 (Box 31, Folder 416)
  - Cox, William R., "Appointment in Vegas," "The Outlawed,", 1958-1960 (Box 31, Folder 417)
  - Coyle, David Cushman, general correspondence, 1955-1961 (Box 32, Folder 418)
  - Coyle, David Cushman, "The United Nations and How it Works,", 1953-1954 (Box 32, Folder 419)
  - Coyle, David Cushman, "The United Nations and How it Works,", 1955-1956 (Box 32, Folder 420)
  - Coyle, David Cushman, "The United Nations and How it Works,", 1957-1961 (Box 32, Folder 421)
  - Coyle, David Cushman, "The United Nations and How it Works,", 1955 (Box 32, Folder 422)
  - Coyle, David Cushman, "The United Nations and How it Works,", 1953-1960 (Box 32, Folder 423)
  - Coyle, David Cushman, "The U.S. Political System and How it Works,", 1952-1954 (Box 33, Folder 424)
  - Coyle, David Cushman, "The U.S. Political System and How it Works,", 1955-1961 (Box 33, Folder 425)
  - Crane, Stephen, "The Red Badge of Courage,", 1959-1961 (Box 33, Folder 426)
  - Crane, Stephen, "The Red Badge of Courage,", 1959-1961 (Box 33, Folder 427)
  - Creekmore, Hubert, "The Chain in the Heart," "The Satires of Juvenal," "The Wilderness,", 1951-1955 (Box 33, Folder 428)
  - Creel, H.G., "Chinese Thought,", 1959 (Box 33, Folder 429)
  - Crevecoeur, St. John de, "Letters from an American Farmer,", 1961 (Box 33, Folder 430)
  - Crockett, Davy, "The Life of Davy Crockett", undated (Box 33, Folder 431)
  - Crofts, Freeman Willis, "The Cask,", 1945-1947 (Box 33, Folder 432)
  - Crompton, John, "The Hunting Wasp," "The Life of the Spider," "The Way of the Ant,", 1951-1958 (Box 33, Folder 433)
  - Cross, Beverley, "The Nightwalkers,", 1958 (Box 33, Folder 434)
  - Croy, Homer, "Last of the Great Outlaws,", 1956-1959 (Box 33, Folder 435)
  - Cunliffe, Marcus, general correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 33, Folder 436)
  - Cunliffe, Marcus, "George Washington,", 1958-1960 (Box 33, Folder 437)
  - Cunliffe, Marcus, "George Washington,", 1955-1957 (Box 33, Folder 438)
  - Cunliffe, Marcus, "George Washington,", 1955-1957 (Box 33, Folder 439)
  - Cunningham, Eugene, "Whistling Lead,", 1949-1958 (Box 33, Folder 440)
  - Czarnomsky, F.B., "The Eloquence of Winston Churchill,", 1957 (Box 33, Folder 441)
  - Daniel-Rops, "Jesus and His Times,", 1954 (Box 33, Folder 442)
  - Daniels, John [Wayne D. Overholser], general correspondence, "The Crossing," "The Gunfighters,", 1958-1960 (Box 33, Folder 443)
  - Daniels, John, "The Man from Yesterday,", 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 444)
  - Daniels, John, "Smoke of the Gun," "Ute Country,", 1957-1959 (Box 33, Folder 445)
  - Darrell, R.D., "Good Listening,", 1952-1957 (Box 33, Folder 446)
  - Darwin, Charles, "The Origin of Species,", 1956-1960 (Box 33, Folder 447)
  - Daugherty, Kermit, "Out of the Red Brush,", 1953-1955 (Box 33, Folder 448)
  - Davies, A.. Powell, general correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 449)
  - Davies, A.. Powell, "Big Bible Book,", 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 450)
  - Davies, A.. Powell, "The First Christian,", 1956-1959 (Box 33, Folder 451)
  - Davies, A.. Powell, "The Meaning of the Dead Sea Scrolls,", 1956 (Box 33, Folder 452)
  - Davies, A.. Powell, "The Meaning of the Dead Sea Scrolls,", 1956-1961 (Box 33, Folder 453)
  - Davies, A.. Powell, "The Ten Commandments,", 1956-1960 (Box 33, Folder 454)
  - Davis, Gwen, general correspondence, undated (Box 33, Folder 455)
  - Dayan, Yael, "New Face in the Mirror,", 1960 (Box 33, Folder 456)
  - Deal, Borden, "Killer in the House,", 1956-1961 (Box 33, Folder 457)
  - Dean, Abner, "What Am I Doing Here,", 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 458)
  - Dean, Vera Micheles, "The Nature of the Non-Western World,", 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 459)
  - Dean, Vera Micheles, "The Nature of the Non-Western World,", 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 460)
  - Dean, Vera Micheles, "The Nature of the Non-Western World,", 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 461)
  - Dean, Vera Micheles, "The Nature of the Non-Western World" (no date), undated (Box 34, Folder 462)
  - Dedman, Julien, "At the Office", undated (Box 34, Folder 463)
  - Defoe, Daniel, "A Journal of the Plague Year", undated (Box 34, Folder 464)
  - Defoe, Daniel, "Robinson Crusoe", undated (Box 34, Folder 465)
  - De la Fayette, Maria, "The Princesse of Cleves,", 1961 (Box 34, Folder 466)
  - Dennis, Patrick, "Around the World with Auntie Mame,", 1959 (Box 34, Folder 467)
  - De Pereda, Prudencio, "All the Girls We Loved,", 1946-1959 (Box 34, Folder 468)
  - Desmond, Warren [Herbert Dyson Carter], "Night of Flame,", 1949 (Box 34, Folder 469)
  - De Vries, Peter, "Comfort Me with Apples,", 1957-1958 (Box 34, Folder 470)
  - De Vries, Peter, "The Mackerel Plaza,", 1958-1960 (Box 34, Folder 471)
  - De Vries, Peter, "No But I Saw the Movie,", 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 472)
  - De Vries, Peter, "Tents of Wickedness,", 1960 (Box 34, Folder 473)
  - De Vries, Peter, "Through the Fields of Clover,", 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 474)
  - De Vries, Peter, "Tunnel of Love,", 1957-1958 (Box 34, Folder 475)
  - Dewey, John, "Reconstruction in Philosophy,", 1948-1960 (Box 34, Folder 476)
  - Dewey, Thomas B., "Dame in Danger," et. al., 1946-1958 (Box 34, Folder 477)
  - Dewlen, Al, "Latitude 18,", 1956-1961 (Box 34, Folder 478)
  - Dewlen, Al, "Night of the Tiger,", 1956-1961 (Box 34, Folder 479)
  - Dewlen, Al, "Twilight of Honor,", 1959-1961 (Box 34, Folder 480)
  - Dickens, Charles, "Hard Times," "Mystery of Edwin Drood,", 1961 (Box 34, Folder 481)
  - Dickens, Charles, "A Tale of Two Cities,", 1959-1961 (Box 34, Folder 482)
  - Dickinson, Patric, "Virgil's Aeneid,", 1961 (Box 34, Folder 483)
  - Dickinson, Patric, "Virgil's Aeneid,", 1957-1961 (Box 34, Folder 484)
  - Dickinson, Patric, "Virgil's Aeneid", undated (Box 34, Folder 485)
  - DiMaggio, Joe, "Baseball for Everyone,", 1948-1950 (Box 34, Folder 486)
  - Dimont, Max, "Jews, Jehovah, and History,", 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 487)
  - Dingwall, Eric J., "The American Woman,", 1956-1959 (Box 34, Folder 488)
  - Dingwall, Eric J., "The Unknown - Is It Nearer?", 1956-1957 (Box 34, Folder 489)
  - Dingwall, Eric J., "The Unknown - Is It Nearer?", 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 490)
  - Dingwall, Eric J., "The Unknown - Is It Nearer?", 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 491)
  - Disraeli, Benjamin, "Coningsby,", 1961 (Box 34, Folder 492)
  - Doctorow, E.L., "Welcome to Hard Times,", 1960 (Box 34, Folder 493)
  - Dodge, Gil [Hano, Arnold], "Flint,", 1956-1958 (Box 34, Folder 494)
  - d'Olive, Gene, "Chiara,", 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 495)
  - Dooley, Tom, trilogy, 1958-1961 (Box 34, Folder 496)
  - Dooley, Tom, "Deliver Us From Evil," "Edge of Tomorrow," "The Night They Burned the Mountain,", 1960-1961 (Box 34, Folder 497)
  - Donahue, Jack, "Someone to Hate", undated (Box 34, Folder 498)
  - Dostoevsky, Feodor, "Crime and Punishment,", 1947-1955 (Box 34, Folder 499)
  - Downs, Robert B., "Books That Changed the World,", 1956-1961 (Box 34, Folder 500)
  - Downs, Robert B., "Books That Changed the World,", 1955 (Box 34, Folder 501)
  - Downs, Robert B., "Books That Changed the World,", 1954 (Box 34, Folder 502)
  - Downs, Robert B., "Books That Changed the World,", 1956-1959 (Box 34, Folder 503)
  - Dreiser, Theodore, "An American Tragedy,", 1949-1958 (Box 34, Folder 504)
  - Dreiser, Theodore, general correspondence, 1944-1958 (Box 34, Folder 505)
  - Duden Dictionary, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 506)
  - Dudley, D.R., "The Civilization of Rome,", 1958-1961 (Box 34, Folder 507)
  - Dudley, D.R., "The Civilization of Rome" (no date), undated (Box 34, Folder 508)
  - Dudley, D.R., "The Civilization of Rome" (no date), undated (Box 34, Folder 509)
  - Duerrenmatt, Friedrich, "The Pledge,", 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 510)
  - Duncan, David, "Wives and Husbands,", 1951-1953 (Box 35, Folder 511)
  - Duncan, Robert, "If It Moves, Salute It,", 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 512)
  - Duncan, Thomas, "Big Man, Big River,", 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 513)
  - Dundee, Robert [Robert R. Kirsch], general correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 35, Folder 514)
  - Dundee, Robert [Robert R. Kirsch], "Inferno," "Pandora's Box," "The Novel in English,", 1959-1961 (Box 35, Folder 515)
  - Dundee, Robert [Robert R. Kirsch], "Restless Lovers,", 1958-1960 (Box 35, Folder 516)
  - Dundy, Elaine, "The Dud Avocado,", 1958-1960 (Box 35, Folder 517.A)
  - Dunn, Harold, "Those Crazy Mixed-Up Kids", undated (Box 35, Folder 517.B)
  - Dunn, L.C., "Heredity, Race and Society,", 1952-1962 (Box 35, Folder 518)
  - Dunn, L.C., "Heredity, Race and Society,", 1947-1959 (Box 35, Folder 519)
  - Dunn, L.C., "Heredity, Race and Society,", 1947-1951 (Box 35, Folder 520)
  - Dunnigan, Ann, "Chekov Stories,", 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 521)
  - Dunnigan, Ann, "Tolstoy Reader,", 1960 (Box 35, Folder 522)
  - Du Nouy, Lecomte, "Human Destiny,", 1949-1960 (Box 35, Folder 523)
  - Dupont, Gene, "The Twenty Year Man,", 1960 (Box 35, Folder 524)
  - Duras, Marguerite, "The Whispers of Love" ["The Sea Wall"], 1952-1959 (Box 35, Folder 525)
  - Durrell, Lawrence, general correspondence, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 526)
  - Eaton, Frank, "Pistol Pete,", 1952-1956 (Box 36, Folder 527)
  - Egner, Robert E., "Bertrand Russell's Best", undated (Box 36, Folder 528)
  - Ekert Rotholz, Alice, "The Time of the Dragon,", 1958-1960 (Box 36, Folder 529)
  - Eliot, Alexander, "Proud Youth,", 1952-1958 (Box 36, Folder 530)
  - Eliot, George, "Adam Bede," "Silas Marner" [afterward: Walter Allen], 1959-1961 (Box 36, Folder 531)
  - Eliot, Thomas Stearns, "The Confidential Clerk" [playbill], 1953 (Box 36, Folder 532)
  - Elliott, George P., "Parktilden Village,", 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 533)
  - Ellis, Havelock, "On Life and Sex: Essays on Love and Virtue,"1956-57, 1956-1957 (Box 36, Folder 534)
  - Ellis, Havelock, "Psychology of Sex,", 1953-1959 (Box 36, Folder 535)
  - Ellison, James Whitfield, general correspondence, "I'm Owen Harrison Harding,", 1955-1959 (Box 36, Folder 536)
  - Ellison, Ralph, "The Invisible Man,", 1951-1960 (Box 36, Folder 537)
  - Engstrand, Stuart, general correspondence, 1950-1955 (Box 36, Folder 538)
  - Engstrand, Stuart, "Beyond the Forest,", 1951-1955 (Box 36, Folder 539)
  - Engstrand, Stuart, "A Husband in the House,", 1951-1955 (Box 36, Folder 540)
  - Engstrand, Stuart, "The Invaders,", 1950-1957 (Box 36, Folder 541)
  - Engstrand, Stuart, "More Death than One,", 1955-1957 (Box 36, Folder 542)
  - Engstrand, Stuart, "The Scattered Seed" ["The Build-Up"], 1952-1956 (Box 36, Folder 543)
  - Engstrand, Stuart, "The Sling and the Arrow,", 1947-1961 (Box 36, Folder 544)
  - Engstrand, Stuart, "Son of the Giant,", 1950-1957 (Box 36, Folder 545)
  - Engstrand, Stuart, "They Sought for Paradise,", 1950-1956 (Box 36, Folder 546)
  - Ermine, Will, general correspondence, "Brave in the Saddle," "Buckskin Marshall,", 1949-1958 (Box 36, Folder 547)
  - Ermine, Will, "Laramie Rides Alone," "Lobo Law,", 1955-1957 (Box 36, Folder 548)
  - Ernenwein, Leslie, "Gunhawk Hawk," "Hell for Leather,", 1950-1958 (Box 36, Folder 549)
  - Ernenwein, Leslie, "Horseshoe Combine" ["Gunsmoke"], "Trigger Justice,", 1949-1956 (Box 36, Folder 550)
  - Erni, Hans [artist], 1955 (Box 36, Folder 551)
  - Escher, Franklin, "A Brief History of the United States,", 1953-1961 (Box 36, Folder 552)
  - Escher, Franklin, "A Brief History of the United States,", 1953-1954 (Box 36, Folder 553)
  - Esslin, Martin, "Mentor Book on 20th Century Drama,", 1960 (Box 36, Folder 554)
  - Eunston, Robert, "The S.O.B.'s,", 1958-1960 (Box 36, Folder 555)
  - Eunston, Robert, "The S.O.B.'s,", 1959-1961 (Box 36, Folder 556)
  - Eunson, Robert, "Tomorrow's Wind" ["Incident at Sengoku" and "Trial at Odiwara"], 1961 (Box 36, Folder 557)
  - Eustis, Marjorie, "The Home Decorator,", 1955-1958 (Box 36, Folder 558)
  - Evans, Evan [Max Brand], "Montana Rides,", 1946-1956 (Box 36, Folder 559)
  - Evans, Evan [Max Brand], "Montana Rides Again," "Song of the Whip,", 1947-1961 (Box 36, Folder 560)
  - Evans, Frederic, "The Death of Innocence,", 1960 (Box 36, Folder 561)
  - Ewen, David, "Music for the Millions,", 1949-1952 (Box 36, Folder 562)
  - Fadiman, Edwin, general correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 36, Folder 563)
  - Fadiman, Edwin, "An Act of Violence," "Byroad,", 1956-1959 (Box 36, Folder 564)
  - Fadiman, Edwin, "The Glass Play-Pen,", 1955-1959 (Box 36, Folder 565)